<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MAD Project</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the">I agree to the</string>
    <string name="community_guidelines"><u>Community Guidelines</u></string>
    <string name="terms_of_service"><u>Terms of Service</u></string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="gender"><u>Gender</u></string>
    <string name="birthday"><u>Birthday</u></string>
    <string name="complete_your_profile">Complete Your Profile</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="guidelines_welcome">Welcome to <b>Soluna</b>, a platform dedicated to empowering individuals, supporting gender equality, and promoting women’s health. We’ve created a space where everyone is encouraged to learn, share, and grow while maintaining a safe and respectful environment. These Community Guidelines will help us protect the values that make <b>Soluna</b> unique. By using <b>Soluna</b>, you agree to adhere to these guidelines and our Terms of Use. We ask you to actively help maintain our supportive, inclusive, and respectful community.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_users">Our community thrives on diversity, and we are committed to fostering an environment where everyone feels safe, respected, and empowered. <b>Soluna</b> is built to support discussions, education, and advocacy around <b>gender equality</b>, <b>women\'s health</b>, and <b>female empowerment</b>. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination or harassment based on gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, religion, nationality, or any other identity characteristic.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_sharing_content"><b>Soluna</b> is a space to share personal experiences, educational resources, and support. We encourage you to share content related to gender equality, female health, and important issues affecting women and marginalized genders. However, all content must align with these guidelines:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_interactions">We want <b>Soluna</b> to be a place for positive, meaningful conversations that help raise awareness, educate, and support one another. Please follow these guidelines to help us maintain a healthy community:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_intellectual">You retain ownership of your content on <b>Soluna</b>, but you must respect the intellectual property of others. Share only content you have the right to post. Do not post copyrighted materials (e.g., images, videos, and text) without permission.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_compliance"><b>Soluna</b> is a place for fostering knowledge and sharing information. We do not tolerate illegal or harmful activities.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_violence">We are committed to creating a supportive environment. We do not tolerate hate speech, violence, or threats of harm based on gender, race, sexuality, or any personal characteristic.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_newsworthy">We understand that important events and news related to gender equality and women’s health are shared on <b>Soluna</b>. While we encourage education and awareness, please be mindful of the following:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_support">We are all part of the <b>Soluna</b> community. If you see content that may violate these guidelines, please report it using the app’s reporting feature. Our team will review the report and take action as necessary to maintain a safe and respectful environment.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_conclusion">We want <b>Soluna</b> to be a safe and empowering platform for everyone. These guidelines are here to help us protect and nurture our community. Together, we can foster an environment where everyone can engage, learn, and grow in the pursuit of gender equality and better health for all. Thank you for being part of the <b>Soluna</b> community.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_ending">By adhering to these guidelines, you are contributing to a supportive space where gender equality, women’s health, and safety are prioritized. We are grateful for your participation in creating a positive and empowering environment for all.</string>

    <string name="terms_welcome">Welcome to <b>Soluna</b>! These Terms of Service ("Terms") govern your access to and use of the <b>Soluna</b> platform, including our website, mobile application, and other online services (collectively referred to as the "Service"). By accessing or using the Service, you agree to comply with these Terms and our Community Guidelines. If you do not agree, you may not use the Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptance">By creating an account or using the Service, you confirm that you are at least 13 years old and legally capable of entering into these Terms. If you are under 18, you must have the consent of a parent or guardian.</string>
    <string name="terms_creation">To use certain features of <b>Soluna</b>, you must create an account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials and for all activities that occur under your account.</string>
    <string name="terms_participation">By using <b>Soluna</b>, you agree to follow our Community Guidelines. These guidelines are designed to create a respectful and empowering environment for all users.</string>
    <string name="terms_content">You retain ownership of the content you post on <b>Soluna</b>. By posting, you grant <b>Soluna</b> a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, distribute, modify, and display your content as necessary to operate the Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_reporting">If you believe content violates your rights or our guidelines, you may report it using the app’s reporting feature.</string>
    <string name="terms_privacy"><b>Soluna</b> collects and uses personal data as described in our Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you consent to our data practices.</string>
    <string name="terms_termination">We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your account if you violate these Terms, our Community Guidelines, or any applicable law. You may also terminate your account at any time by contacting our support team.</string>
    <string name="terms_dispute">If disputes arise, they will be resolved through binding arbitration, subject to the laws of the jurisdiction where <b>Soluna</b> operates.</string>
    <string name="terms_changes">We may update these Terms from time to time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting. Continued use of the Service constitutes acceptance of the updated Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms_contact">For questions about these Terms, you can reach us at support@<b>Soluna</b>.com.</string>
    <string name="terms_thanks">Thank you for being a part of the <b>Soluna</b> community. Together, we’re creating a supportive and empowering space for all.</string>
</resources>