<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Soluna</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the">I agree to the</string>
    <string name="community_guidelines"><u>Community Guidelines</u></string>
    <string name="terms_of_service"><u>Terms of Service</u></string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="gender"><u>Gender</u></string>
    <string name="birthday"><u>Birthday</u></string>
    <string name="complete_your_profile">Complete Your Profile</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="guidelines_welcome">Welcome to <b>Soluna</b>, a platform dedicated to empowering individuals, supporting gender equality, and promoting women’s health. We’ve created a space where everyone is encouraged to learn, share, and grow while maintaining a safe and respectful environment. These Community Guidelines will help us protect the values that make <b>Soluna</b> unique. By using <b>Soluna</b>, you agree to adhere to these guidelines and our Terms of Use. We ask you to actively help maintain our supportive, inclusive, and respectful community.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_users">Our community thrives on diversity, and we are committed to fostering an environment where everyone feels safe, respected, and empowered. <b>Soluna</b> is built to support discussions, education, and advocacy around <b>gender equality</b>, <b>women\'s health</b>, and <b>female empowerment</b>. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination or harassment based on gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, religion, nationality, or any other identity characteristic.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_sharing_content"><b>Soluna</b> is a space to share personal experiences, educational resources, and support. We encourage you to share content related to gender equality, female health, and important issues affecting women and marginalized genders. However, all content must align with these guidelines:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_interactions">We want <b>Soluna</b> to be a place for positive, meaningful conversations that help raise awareness, educate, and support one another. Please follow these guidelines to help us maintain a healthy community:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_intellectual">You retain ownership of your content on <b>Soluna</b>, but you must respect the intellectual property of others. Share only content you have the right to post. Do not post copyrighted materials (e.g., images, videos, and text) without permission.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_compliance"><b>Soluna</b> is a place for fostering knowledge and sharing information. We do not tolerate illegal or harmful activities.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_violence">We are committed to creating a supportive environment. We do not tolerate hate speech, violence, or threats of harm based on gender, race, sexuality, or any personal characteristic.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_respect_newsworthy">We understand that important events and news related to gender equality and women’s health are shared on <b>Soluna</b>. While we encourage education and awareness, please be mindful of the following:</string>
    <string name="guidelines_support">We are all part of the <b>Soluna</b> community. If you see content that may violate these guidelines, please report it using the app’s reporting feature. Our team will review the report and take action as necessary to maintain a safe and respectful environment.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_conclusion">We want <b>Soluna</b> to be a safe and empowering platform for everyone. These guidelines are here to help us protect and nurture our community. Together, we can foster an environment where everyone can engage, learn, and grow in the pursuit of gender equality and better health for all. Thank you for being part of the <b>Soluna</b> community.</string>
    <string name="guidelines_ending">By adhering to these guidelines, you are contributing to a supportive space where gender equality, women’s health, and safety are prioritized. We are grateful for your participation in creating a positive and empowering environment for all.</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>

    <!-- FAQ section -->
    <string name="faq_1_question">How do I create an account on Soluna?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_answer">To create an account, download the Soluna app. Click on “Sign Up” and follow the prompts to enter your email and set a password. If you encounter any issues, ensure your email address is valid or contact support at support@soluna.com.</string>

    <string name="faq_2_question">What should I do if I forget my password?</string>
    <string name="faq_2_answer">Use the “Forgot Password” option on the login page. Enter your registered email address, and you are able to reset your password now.</string>

    <string name="faq_3_question">Can I access my Soluna account from multiple devices?</string>
    <string name="faq_3_answer">Yes, you can access your Soluna account from multiple devices, including smartphones, tablets, and computers. Simply log in using the same credentials on any device.</string>

    <string name="faq_4_question">How do I update my profile information?</string>
    <string name="faq_4_answer">To update your profile, open the Soluna app, go to your profile section, and click on the “Edit Profile” button. From there, you can change your name, profile picture, and other personal details.</string>

    <string name="faq_5_question">What type of content am I allowed to post?</string>
    <string name="faq_5_answer">You can post educational, supportive, and authentic content related to gender equality, women’s health, and empowerment. Avoid posting anything that violates intellectual property rights or contains hate speech.</string>

    <string name="faq_6_question">Are there any restrictions on posting links?</string>
    <string name="faq_6_answer">You can post links to relevant educational or supportive content. However, links that lead to malicious sites, spam, or unrelated advertisements are not allowed and may result in your post being removed.</string>

    <string name="faq_7_question">What is the Soluna Community Guidelines?</string>
    <string name="faq_7_answer">The Soluna Community Guidelines outline the behaviors and content that are not allowed on the platform. This includes hate speech, discrimination, explicit content, and harmful behavior. You can view the full guidelines in the app.</string>

    <string name="faq_8_question">Can I share my account with others?</string>
    <string name="faq_8_answer">Each Soluna account is meant to be used by an individual only. Sharing your account is against our terms of service and may lead to suspension or termination of your account. Please keep your account details secure.</string>

    <string name="faq_9_question">How do I ensure my privacy while using Soluna?</string>
    <string name="faq_9_answer">Avoid sharing sensitive personal information such as your address or phone number publicly. Review our Privacy Policy for tips on managing your privacy settings.</string>

    <string name="faq_10_question">How can I contact support?</string>
    <string name="faq_10_answer">You can contact Soluna support by emailing us at support@soluna.com. Be sure to provide as much detail as possible about your issue to help us assist you quickly.</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="account_settings">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="description_show_notification">Toggles whether notifications from the app are displayed at all. Turning this off will disable all notifications for the app.</string>
    <string name="show_notifications">Show notifications</string>
    <string name="description_floating_notification">Allows notifications to appear as floating pop-ups on the screen, even when you\'re using other apps.</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="floating_notifications">Floating notifications</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_notifications">Lock screen notifications</string>
    <string name="description_lock_screen_notification">Controls whether notifications are shown on the lock screen. You can keep it on to view notifications without unlocking your phone.</string>
    <string name="allow_vibration">Allow vibration</string>
    <string name="description_allow_vibration">Activates vibration for notifications. Useful for receiving haptic feedback when a notification arrives.</string>
    <string name="description_allow_sound">Enables sound to play when a notification is received. Turn it off for silent notifications.</string>
    <string name="allow_sound">Allow sound</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="current_password">Current Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>


    <string name="terms_welcome">Welcome to <b>Soluna</b>! These Terms of Service ("Terms") govern your access to and use of the <b>Soluna</b> platform, including our website, mobile application, and other online services (collectively referred to as the "Service"). By accessing or using the Service, you agree to comply with these Terms and our Community Guidelines. If you do not agree, you may not use the Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptance">By creating an account or using the Service, you confirm that you are at least 13 years old and legally capable of entering into these Terms. If you are under 18, you must have the consent of a parent or guardian.</string>
    <string name="terms_creation">To use certain features of <b>Soluna</b>, you must create an account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials and for all activities that occur under your account.</string>
    <string name="terms_participation">By using <b>Soluna</b>, you agree to follow our Community Guidelines. These guidelines are designed to create a respectful and empowering environment for all users.</string>
    <string name="terms_content">You retain ownership of the content you post on <b>Soluna</b>. By posting, you grant <b>Soluna</b> a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, distribute, modify, and display your content as necessary to operate the Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_reporting">If you believe content violates your rights or our guidelines, you may report it using the app’s reporting feature.</string>
    <string name="terms_privacy"><b>Soluna</b> collects and uses personal data as described in our Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you consent to our data practices.</string>
    <string name="terms_termination">We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your account if you violate these Terms, our Community Guidelines, or any applicable law. You may also terminate your account at any time by contacting our support team.</string>
    <string name="terms_dispute">If disputes arise, they will be resolved through binding arbitration, subject to the laws of the jurisdiction where <b>Soluna</b> operates.</string>
    <string name="terms_changes">We may update these Terms from time to time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting. Continued use of the Service constitutes acceptance of the updated Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms_contact">For questions about these Terms, you can reach us at support@<b>Soluna</b>.com.</string>
    <string name="terms_thanks">Thank you for being a part of the <b>Soluna</b> community. Together, we’re creating a supportive and empowering space for all.</string>
</resources>